<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on </title>
    <link>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:59:37 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/categories123/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:59:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/categories123/</guid>
      <description>fasdfdaafadfadfasdfsd</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicolás Astorga</title>
      <link>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:59:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>My ML objective I am an ML researcher that is passionate, really passionate, about machine learning. I want to develop models capable of extracting the most information from all available data sources. At the same time, I want these models to generalize. In this development process I want to learn the most and help humanity using these autonomous models.
Research interests I think that to develop such general models it is necesary to learn various ML subdisciplines: generative models, ML architectures, RL, transfer learning, causal structure learning, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:59:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/research/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of current work from my thesis that I have not published yet. I currently working with Pablo Huijse, Pavlos Protopapas and Pablo Estévez to make this work available as papers. You can have an idea of this work here. The following work is already published.
Publications  Nicolas Astorga, Pablo Huijse, Pavlos Protopapas and Pablo A. Estévez. “MPCC: Matching Priors and Conditionals for clustering”, European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), Glasglow, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at ALeRCE</title>
      <link>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 15:59:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jumpynitro.github.io/blog/industry/</guid>
      <description>Currently, I am working part-time in ALeRCE (Automatic Learning for the Rapid Classification of Events) as machine learning engineer. ALeRCE is a Chilean-led broker that process alert streams of astronomical data. The amount of astronomical data is huge and autonomous mechanisms are necessary to detect new interesting astronoimcal objects (note, we can not put a bunch of astronomers to look images of the sky). Being part of ALeRCE is my closest attempt to engineering, and it has been an entertaining journey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
